businessmagnet.co.uk 2017-01-27

# Businessmagnet Directory | Privacy Policy

Businessmagnet Limited respects the privacy rights of our users and is strongly committed to protecting your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to this Web site and does not apply to other products or services of Businessmagnet Limited, its general and limited partners, and any other subsidiaries.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data that you provide to us or we collect, will be handled and processed by us. Please read the following, it describes our practices and views regarding your personal data and how we treat it.   
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 the data controller is Businessmagnet Limited of 9 Meadway Court, Meadway Technology Park, Stevenage, Hertfordshire SG1 2EF

**INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU**  
We may collect the following data from you: 

  * When you visit our site we automatically log your browser type, the country you are from and your access times and pages on an internal (secured) statistics page (Log File). We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data ( the pages our users visit on our site ). This data helps us to determine what contents are thought of as most appealing by our visitors, so with that we can maximize your experience of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.businessmagnet.co.uk. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site for controlling purposes, subscribing to our services, posting comments, content or requesting further information. We may sometimes ask for further information if you report any issues you may have with our site

  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of conversations and correspondence.

  * From time to time we may ask you to engage in a survey for research purposes. We use this data to build demographic information. You do not have to complete any survey if you so wish.

  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

**STORAGE OF PERSONAL DATA**  
Businessmagnet Limited will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.   
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. We do not request or handle online payments . Some areas of the site require log-in access that is password protected. Your password enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password safe and confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.   
Information transmitted over the internet is not completely secure. Businessmagnet will do its best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information however, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

**IP ADDRESSES AND COOKIES**   
We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type. This is usual data that is collected where log files are in use. This is statistical data about our users� browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual. The information is used to create demographic patterns and overall user behaviour patters to better inform our visitors. We may obtain information about your use of our site by using a cookie file which is stored on your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computers hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. We use cookies to identify you when you return to our site, this enables us to be more accurate about our site usage and browsing behaviour. The use of cookies allows us to more accurately estimate our audience size.   
You can refuse to accept cookies if you wish by selecting the setting on your browser which allows you to deny the setting of a cookie. Unless you have adjusted the above settings so that cookies are refused, our system will issue cookie when you log on to our site. Some of our advertisers may use cookies on there own sites, we have no control over this as they are external to our site.

**MORE ABOUT COOKIES**  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that sites computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser�s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies that originate from their sites. We have no access or control over those cookies. 

**WHAT IS A LOG FILE?**  
A log file is a recording of everything that goes in and out of a particular server. It is a concept much like the black box of an airplane that records everything going on with the plane in the event of a problem. The information is frequently recorded chronologically, and is located in the root directory, or occasionally in a secondary folder, depending on how it is set up with the server. The only person who has regular access to the log files of a server is the server administrator, and a log file is generally password protected, so that the server administrator has a record of everyone and everything that wants to look at the log files for a specific server.

**USE OF INFORMATION**  
We may use information held about you to allow you to use interactive elements and features of our site, to carry out any obligations arising from any contacts between us and you, to present information in the most effective way for you and your computer. We may also use this information to notify you about changes to our services. 

**THIRD PARTIES**  
We do not pass on your personal details for marketing purposes that you may have supplied to us and we do not disclose information about identifiable individuals to our advertisers or users. Combined, demographical information may be used to target specific audiences for our advertisers. 

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**  
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985.

Businessmagnet Limited may disclose your personal information to affiliates or unaffiliated third parties if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary: (a) to comply with the law or in response to a court order, government request, or other legal process; (b) to protect the interests, rights, safety, or property of Businessmagnet Limited or others; (c) to enforce any terms of service on this Web site; (d) to provide you with the services or products requested by you (including allowing a purchaser of Businessmagnet Limited to continue to serve you), and to perform other activities related to such services and products, including billing and collection; (e) to provide you with information, special offers, or promotions from Businessmagnet Limited to which you consented; or (f) to operate Businessmagnets systems properly. Businessmagnet Limited makes reasonable efforts to limit its designated service providers disclosure of your personal information in the same manner as set forth in this paragraph.

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**  
Businessmagnet does provide links to third-party Web sites. Since we do not control third-party sites and are not responsible for any personal information you may provide while on such sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those Web sites before providing any of your personal information on such sites.

**COMMUNICATIONS**  
If you contact us, the webmaster will always reply to serious messages. We will not respond to all kinds of internet pollution including spam, cold marketers and the like.

**HOW CAN YOU ACCESS AND CORRECT YOUR INFORMATION?**  
Aside from the facilities we provide to amend, append, add and edit, you may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing [ customerservices@businessmagnet.co.uk](mailto:customerservices@businessmagnet.co.uk)

**MODIFICATIONS TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
Businessmagnet Limited reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions on this Web page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.
